<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-06-29T15:30:23-05:00</updated><id>https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Samaya</title><subtitle>CSA</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Recursion Lesson</title><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/ap/2023/06/28/recursion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recursion Lesson" /><published>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/ap/2023/06/28/recursion</id><author><name></name></author><category term="AP" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Title</title><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/Untitled.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Title" /><published>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/Untitled</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Letter Of Rec</title><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/Letter-of-Rec.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Letter Of Rec" /><published>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/Letter-of-Rec</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experiences]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Csusm Extra Credit</title><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/CSUSM-Extra-Credit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Csusm Extra Credit" /><published>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/CSUSM-Extra-Credit</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[While this might have been a promo for Cal State University San Marcos, I am genuinely grateful for being able to attend this event, learn about the presenters Ashley and John, gain more knowledge about college in general, and have hands-on experience. Beginning with Ashley, she explained how she majored in Applied Physics while failing her AP Physics class. This really resonated with me because even though I am not failing physics it is still a difficult class for me. This showed me that even though I may find topics I struggle with in high school, I can still pursue them at a higher level if I truly enjoy them. This also applies to computer science, because while I might not be the best at it if I truly want to learn this field at a higher educational level I will be able to if I am dedicated. Ashley also explained how she is trying to get a Ph.D. in material science and engineering which is also interesting to me because her being an Applied Physics major means that it can open doors to many other fields. She also talked about how she uses computer science in her major too (python) and this shows how computer science is such a versatile field that can be applied to other industries. Moving on to John, he explained how straight out of high school he attended Palomar College, then transferred to CSUSM. By explaining this he is showing that there are many different kinds of people that attend CSUSM and it is a college that gives opportunities to everyone. To end their presentation, Ashley and John, let us experiment with making a toothbrush vibrate which was a unique experience, since these events are usually more lecture-style. This helped me understand that I am interested in an engineering or STEM-related field and hopefully I can use this encounter in the future.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Test Corrections</title><link href="https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/Test-Corrections.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test Corrections" /><published>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://samayass.github.io/samayaCSA/2023/06/28/-Test-Corrections</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>